<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Zodiac_App</string>

    <string name="horoscope_name_aries">Aries</string>
    <string name="horoscope_name_taurus">Taurus</string>
    <string name="horoscope_name_gemini">Gemini</string>
    <string name="horoscope_name_cancer">Cancer</string>
    <string name="horoscope_name_leo">Leo</string>
    <string name="horoscope_name_virgo">Virgo</string>
    <string name="horoscope_name_libra">Libra</string>
    <string name="horoscope_name_scorpio">Scorpio</string>
    <string name="horoscope_name_sagittarius">Sagittarius</string>
    <string name="horoscope_name_capricorn">Capricorn</string>
    <string name="horoscope_name_aquarius">Aquarius</string>
    <string name="horoscope_name_pisces">Pisces</string>

    <string name="horoscope_date_aries">March 21 to April 19</string>
    <string name="horoscope_date_taurus">April 20 to May 20</string>
    <string name="horoscope_date_gemini">May 21 to June 20</string>
    <string name="horoscope_date_cancer">June 21 to July 22</string>
    <string name="horoscope_date_leo">July 23 to August 22</string>
    <string name="horoscope_date_virgo">August 23 to September 22</string>
    <string name="horoscope_date_libra">September 23 to October 22</string>
    <string name="horoscope_date_scorpio">October 23 to November 21</string>
    <string name="horoscope_date_sagittarius">November 22 to December 21</string>
    <string name="horoscope_date_capricorn">December 22 to January 19</string>
    <string name="horoscope_date_aquarius">January 20 to February 18</string>
    <string name="horoscope_date_pisces">February 19 to March 20</string>

    <string name="horoscope_desc_aries">Aries is a fire sign known for its courage, energy, and strong determination. They are natural-born leaders who act with confidence and rarely hesitate when facing challenges. Their impulsive nature makes them exciting and dynamic, always ready to start new projects. However, they can sometimes struggle with patience and prefer to take action rather than wait.</string>
    <string name="horoscope_desc_taurus">Taurus is an earth sign deeply connected to stability, comfort, and security. They are incredibly patient, reliable, and persistent, often achieving their goals through steady effort over time. Taurus individuals appreciate beauty, pleasure, and a peaceful environment. However, they can also be quite stubborn and resistant to sudden change.</string>
    <string name="horoscope_desc_gemini">Gemini is an air sign known for curiosity, adaptability, and excellent communication skills. They are social, witty, and love exchanging ideas with others, making them very engaging companions. Their dual nature allows them to see multiple perspectives, but it can also make them indecisive at times. Gemini thrives in dynamic environments where there is always something new to learn.</string>
    <string name="horoscope_desc_cancer">Cancer is a water sign deeply connected to emotions, intuition, and family life. They are nurturing, protective, and highly empathetic, often putting the needs of others before their own. Home and close relationships are extremely important to them, giving them emotional security. However, they can be sensitive and may retreat into their shell when feeling hurt.</string>
    <string name="horoscope_desc_leo">Leo is a fire sign associated with confidence, charisma, and natural leadership. They love to express themselves and often shine in social situations where they can inspire others. Generous and warm-hearted, Leo enjoys making people feel appreciated and valued. At times, they may seek attention and recognition, but their intentions are usually sincere.</string>
    <string name="horoscope_desc_virgo">Virgo is an earth sign known for precision, intelligence, and strong analytical thinking. They are highly detail-oriented and strive for perfection in everything they do. Virgos are practical problem-solvers who enjoy helping others improve and grow. However, their high standards can sometimes make them overly critical of themselves and others.</string>
    <string name="horoscope_desc_libra">Libra is an air sign that seeks balance, harmony, and fairness in all aspects of life. They are diplomatic, charming, and naturally skilled at building relationships and resolving conflicts. Libras have a strong appreciation for beauty, art, and elegance. However, their desire to keep everyone happy can sometimes lead to indecision.</string>
    <string name="horoscope_desc_scorpio">Scorpio is a water sign known for emotional depth, intensity, and strong willpower. They are extremely passionate individuals who form deep and meaningful connections with others. Scorpios are highly determined and resilient, often thriving in challenging situations. However, their intensity can sometimes make them secretive or emotionally guarded.</string>
    <string name="horoscope_desc_sagittarius">Sagittarius is a fire sign that represents freedom, exploration, and optimism. They are adventurous spirits who love traveling, learning, and experiencing new cultures. Their positive outlook on life makes them inspiring and fun to be around. However, they can sometimes be restless and struggle with long-term routines or commitments.</string>
    <string name="horoscope_desc_capricorn">Capricorn is an earth sign defined by discipline, ambition, and strong responsibility. They are hardworking individuals who are focused on long-term goals and success. Capricorns are practical, strategic, and highly reliable in both personal and professional life. However, their seriousness can sometimes make them seem reserved or overly focused on work.</string>
    <string name="horoscope_desc_aquarius">Aquarius is an air sign known for originality, independence, and innovative thinking. They often challenge traditional ideas and enjoy exploring unique perspectives. Aquarians are visionaries who care about improving society and helping others. However, they can sometimes appear distant or emotionally detached due to their strong focus on ideas.</string>
    <string name="horoscope_desc_pisces">Pisces is a water sign known for sensitivity, imagination, and deep empathy. They are dreamers with rich inner worlds and strong creative abilities. Pisces individuals are compassionate and often deeply understand the emotions of others. However, they can sometimes become overwhelmed by feelings or escape into fantasy.</string>
</resources>